<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ui on Fore Documentation</title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/tags/ui/</link><description>Recent content in Ui on Fore Documentation</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 16:08:59 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/tags/ui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>&lt;fx-alert></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/alert/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/alert/</guid><description>Description fx-alert element is used for messaging validation errors and may be used within fx-bind element or as a child of a UI control like fx-control.
Attributes No Attributes
Events none
Examples Binding Revalidation</description></item><item><title>The anatomy of Fore</title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/getstarted/mvc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 16:08:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/getstarted/mvc/</guid><description>Before stepping deeper a basic understanding of the main parts of Fore is helpful.
Fore elements fall into 3 categories:
The model elements: the model (&amp;lt;fx-model&amp;gt;) and its children hold the data and their state, calculate, validate and submit the data. The state will be reflected in the UI after a refresh.
The UI elements: establish a two-way binding between a data value and a control. When the user interacts with a UI element it will trigger Actions to change the data in the model or otherwise interact with the UI.</description></item><item><title>UI Elements</title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/</guid><description>This chapter describes all user interface elements.</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-case></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/case/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/case/</guid><description>Description Defines one &amp;lsquo;page&amp;rsquo; of a fx-switch element.
Attributes Name Description label optional label name a unique name to be used with fx-toggle Events Name Description select dispatched to fx-case when a case gets selected deselect dispatched to fx-case when case gets deselected Examples Repeat in Switch TEI header editor sample Switch</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-container></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/container/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/container/</guid><description>&amp;lt;fx-container&amp;gt; is an abstract class used for container controls like &amp;lt;fx-group&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;fx-switch&amp;gt;.</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-control></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/control/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/control/</guid><description>Description fx-control is no concrete control displayed in the browser but instead wraps such a control and binds it to a data node in the model with the help of a ref attribute.
Attributes Name Description Default as &amp;rsquo;text&amp;rsquo; or &amp;rsquo;node&amp;rsquo;. When using &amp;rsquo;node&amp;rsquo; a whole dom tree can be passed to a widget text context XPath reference pointing to parent context incopeContext credentials sets credentials policy - one of &amp;lsquo;omit&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;same-origin&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;include&amp;rsquo; same-origin create if present on control or anchestor will create non-existing attribute nodes in the data - debounce optional numeric value in milliseconds to delay input events - initial XPath binding expression referring to data that get passed to Fore control as default instance.</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-dialog></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/dialog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/dialog/</guid><description>Description Simple modal dialog with arbitrary content.
To be used with fx-show and fx-hide actions.
Attributes Name Description id required to be used by fx-show' and fx-hide`actions Events none
Examples fx-dialog</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-hint></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/hint/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/hint/</guid><description/></item><item><title>&lt;fx-inspector></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/inspector/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/inspector/</guid><description>Description Instance Inspector is a helper element for development which displays all used instances at the bottom of the viewport.
It uses the log() function under the hood and renders a html details element for each instance.
Attributes Name Description default open wether or not to be open by default false Events none
Examples Simple TEI Header editor</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-items></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/items/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/items/</guid><description>Description Helper element to build a list of items by repeating given template for each node in the bound nodeset.
Attributes Name Description ref XPath reference pointing to nodeset to be repeated Events none
Examples Select Multiple</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-output></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/output/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/output/</guid><description>Description Outputs bound or calculated values.
Also supports mimtypes &amp;lsquo;html&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;markdown&amp;rsquo; to render bound nodes accordingly.
Events none
Attributes Name Description Default ref XPath reference pointing to the bound node - value XPath expression calculating a string value mediatype either &amp;lsquo;html&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;markdown&amp;rsquo; are accepted by now. Examples The fx-output Element Get started Instances Instance super powers Binding fx-control</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-repeat></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/repeat/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/repeat/</guid><description>Description Repeats template for each node of the referenced nodeset.
For each data node in the referenced nodeset one &amp;lt;fx-repeatitem&amp;gt; element will be created that will contain the evaluated template as content.
Attributes Name Description id identifier for repeat ref XPath reference pointing to the bound node Events Name Description Details path-mutated dispatched when repeat nodeset changes &amp;lsquo;path&amp;rsquo; - the mutation path &amp;lsquo;index&amp;rsquo; - the index of the changed repeat item.</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-switch></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/switch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/switch/</guid><description>Description Container that has fx-case children of which only one is shown at a given time.
Can be unbound and toggled via an action or bound and react to data value.
Attributes Name Description default ref (optional) binds switch to data node and toggles cases depending on value Events none
Examples auth repeat in switch Simple TEI Header switch</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-trigger></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/trigger/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/ui/trigger/</guid><description>Description Generic container for action buttons, links etc. which can execute an action when activated.
&amp;lt;fx-trigger&amp;gt; can also be bound and therefore become readonly or non-relevant.
Attributes Name Description Default ref XPath reference pointing to the bound node - Examples trigger actions binding delay delay dispatch &amp;hellip;</description></item></channel></rss>