<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>elements actions on Fore Documentation</title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/tags/elements-actions/</link><description>Recent content in elements actions on Fore Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/tags/elements-actions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>&lt;fx-append></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/append/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/append/</guid><description>Description Appends an entry to an fx-repeat.
Note: this is deprecated. Please use fx-insert.
Attributes Name Description ref the XPath ref to append to repeat the fx-repeat to append to Events Name Description index-changed dispatched after entry has been added to a repeat Examples todo nested todo TEI header editor sample</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-confirm></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/confirm/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/confirm/</guid><description>Description Displays simple confirmation dialog. Action will only execute if confirmation returns true.
Attributes Name Description message Message to display for confirmation. Action Attributes Name Description target id reference to element this action attaches to Events none
Examples Project Task planner</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-delete></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/delete/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/delete/</guid><description>Description Deletes a node from a nodeset.
fx-delete Attributes Name Description ref XPath reference to instance node(s) to delete Examples todo nested todo TEI header editor sample</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-dispatch></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/dispatch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/dispatch/</guid><description>Description Action to dispatch an event with optional parameters to specific targets.
To specify event properties the fx-property element is used.
fx-dispatch will use id resolution within fx-repeat elements to resolve the id in scope of current occurence.
Attributes Name Description name name of event to dispatch targetid id reference of element to dispatch to Events none
Examples dispatch with properties fx-dispatch action</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-hide></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/hide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/hide/</guid><description>Description Action to hide a fx-dialog.
Attributes Name Description dialog idref of an fx-dialog element. Examples fx-dialog</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-insert></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/insert/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/insert/</guid><description>Description Action to insert node(s) into instance data.
General Binding Attributes Name Description ref XPath pointing to node(s) the bind is attaching to Attributes Name Description Default at index position in nodeset where to insert new node(s) 0 position with regard to &amp;lsquo;at&amp;rsquo; can be either &amp;lsquo;before&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;after&amp;rsquo; after origin XPath pointing to nodes to be inserted into referenced nodeset keepValues marker attribute. When present will keep text-values of origin nodes Events Name Description insert dispatched when nodes have been inserted detail[insertedNodes] - the inserted nodes detail[position] - the position of the insert in the nodeset Examples Insert into inhomogenious nodeset insert action insert action 2 TEI header editor sample todo the while attribute</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-load></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/load/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/load/</guid><description>Description Loads some content into a page, open a new tab with content or replaces current browser window with content.
Content may be loaded from url or be specified inline surrounded with a template element.
If the HTML being loaded contains a fx-fore element it will be extracted from the page and used as content to be inserted.
Attributes Name Description default attach-to &amp;lsquo;_self&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;_blank&amp;rsquo; or idref prefixed with &amp;lsquo;#&amp;rsquo; _self url URL to load content from Events Name Description url-loaded dispatched after successful load of content Examples load &amp;lsquo;Unloading&amp;rsquo; a section With load you can also delete parts of the DOM and replace them with an empty element.</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-message></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/message/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/message/</guid><description>Description Display a message to the user.
Attributes Name Description default level &amp;lsquo;modal&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;modeless&amp;rsquo; or &amp;rsquo;ephemeral&amp;rsquo; ephemeral &amp;lsquo;modal&amp;rsquo; - modal dialog window &amp;lsquo;sticky&amp;rsquo; - sticky popup message &amp;rsquo;ephemeral&amp;rsquo; - auto-closing popup message default value XPath expression which resolves to message Events none
Examples fx-message actions Binding the delay attribute fx-control Hello World the if attribute instances lazy modelItem creation during UI init the while attribute</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-refresh></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/refresh/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/refresh/</guid><description>Description Triggers immediate refresh.
Attributes Name Description control id of an control to be refreshed explicitly force marker attribute to force a full refresh - overrules control self searches upwards for fx-control and refreshes it Events none
Examples the delay attribute Randomizer the while attribute</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-replace></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/replace/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/replace/</guid><description>Description Replaces a node with another.
Attributes Name Description ref XPath reference pointing to the bound node with XPath expression to point to a node for replacement Examples Replace Action</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-send></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/send/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/send/</guid><description>Description Triggers a submission. Submission with given id must exist otherwise error is thrown.
Attributes Name Description submission required idref to fx-submission element. Also supports &amp;lsquo;#reload&amp;rsquo; which just reloads the window. target overwrites target attribute of submission - may contain template expressions url overwrites url attribute of submission - may contain template expressions Attributes that overwrite submission attributes are set once per execution. Calling the same submission again without such an attribute falls back to the value on fx-submission element.</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-setfocus></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/setfocus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/setfocus/</guid><description>Description Sets the focus to a control with given id. If the id is within an repeat it will look for the active repeatitem and search that for the control.
Since: Version 2.0.0
Attributes Name Description control idref that a control select if attribute is given the value of the control will be selected Events none
Examples todo</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-setvalue></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/setvalue/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/setvalue/</guid><description>Description Sets a value to a bound node.
Attributes Name Description ref XPath reference pointing to the bound node value XPath expression to be set as value Events none
Examples Action auth binding the delay attribute events events 2 hello</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-show></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/show/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/show/</guid><description>Description Action to display a fx-dialog.
Attributes Name Description dialog idref of an fx-dialog element. Events none
Examples fx-dialog</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-toggle></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/toggle/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/toggle/</guid><description>Description Action to toggle a fx-switch element.
Attributes Name Description case id of fx-case element to show Events none
Examples auth repeat in switch Simple TEI Header switch</description></item><item><title>Actions</title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/</guid><description>Action Elements This chapter describes all Action elements.
Common Attributes The following attribues can be used on any Fore action element.
Name Description defaultAction &amp;lsquo;perform&amp;rsquo; (default) or &amp;lsquo;cancel&amp;rsquo; delay delay before action is executed in milliseconds. event the event name this action is listening to if boolean XPath expression. Action is only executed if this returns true. phase &amp;lsquo;default&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;capture&amp;rsquo; propagate &amp;lsquo;stop&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;continue&amp;rsquo; (default) target id of element to attach to or special values &amp;lsquo;#window&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;#document&amp;rsquo; while boolean XPath expression.</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-update></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/update/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/actions/update/</guid><description>Description Triggers an explicit update of the model
Attributes No Attributes
Events none
Examples delay randomizer while</description></item></channel></rss>