<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>model on Fore Documentation</title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/tags/model/</link><description>Recent content in model on Fore Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 16:08:59 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/tags/model/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>&lt;fx-model></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/model/model/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 16:08:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/model/model/</guid><description>Description The model is responsible for:
creating and maintaining the Main Dependency Graph (MDG). creating ModelItems for bound data nodes calculation validation This is done with the help of bind elements.
The &amp;lt;fx-model&amp;gt; element is a direct child of &amp;lt;fx-fore&amp;gt; and is itself a container for:
one or more &amp;lt;fx-instance&amp;gt; elements zero, one or more &amp;lt;fx-bind&amp;gt; elements zero, one or more &amp;lt;fx-submission&amp;gt; elements zero, one or more &amp;lt;fx-function&amp;gt; elements Warning: &amp;lt;fx-model&amp;gt; must be in front of Fore UI elements due to not fully understood Web Components behaviour.</description></item><item><title>The anatomy of Fore</title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/getstarted/mvc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 16:08:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/getstarted/mvc/</guid><description>Before stepping deeper a basic understanding of the main parts of Fore is helpful.
Fore uses a classical Model-View-Controller (MVC) architecture.
There are 3 basic things to remember:
The model (&amp;lt;fx-model&amp;gt;) holds the data and their state. This state will be used during refresh to apply changes to the UI.
When the user interacts with a page the UI will trigger Actions to change the data in the model.
Actions will do the actual mutation of the data like setting a value, replacing, inserting or deleting a data node.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/getstarted/hello/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 16:08:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/getstarted/hello/</guid><description>What can be learned here:
the basic structure of Fore &amp;lt;fx-model&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;fx-instance&amp;gt; elements using a Template Expression Hello World - Step by Step Each &amp;lt;fx-fore&amp;gt; element has a single model.
1. Add the model First step to create a data-bound &amp;lsquo;Hello World&amp;rsquo; example is to add a model.
&amp;lt;fx-fore&amp;gt; &amp;lt;fx-model&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/fx-model&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/fx-fore&amp;gt; The &amp;lt;fx-model&amp;gt; is a direct child of the &amp;lt;fx-fore&amp;gt; element.
2. Add some data Not very exciting so far, so add some data:</description></item><item><title>Model</title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/model/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/model/</guid><description>Model Elements This chapter describes all elements belonging to the Fore Model.
Model elements have no visual representation and are always hidden from view.</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-bind></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/model/bind/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/model/bind/</guid><description>Description The fx-bind element attaches constraints and calculations to instance nodes.
Attributes Name Description Default alert used to specify a message to be displayed when constraints fail - ref XPath pointing to node(s) the bind is attaching to - calculate XPath expression to be calculated. Result will become value of node(s) referenced by ref - constraint boolean XPath expression to determine validity of node(s) true readonly boolean XPath expression to determine readonly/readwrite state false relevant boolean XPath expression to determine relevant/non-relevant state true required boolean XPath expression to determine required/optional state false type datatype - reserved for future versions string Events none</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-function></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/model/functions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/model/functions/</guid><description>Description Allows to define custom inline function in either XPath/XQuery or Javascript.
Attributes Name Description signature the function signature. Must use &amp;rsquo;local&amp;rsquo; prefix type can be &amp;rsquo;text/xpath&amp;rsquo;, &amp;rsquo;text/javascript&amp;rsquo;, &amp;rsquo;text/xquf&amp;rsquo; (XQuery Update Facility) Events none
Examples Xquery Update Facility &amp;lt;fx-function signature=&amp;#34;update($element as element()) as element()*&amp;#34; type=&amp;#34;text/xquf&amp;#34;&amp;gt; copy $xml := $element modify ( for $ref in $xml/element return insert node $ref/@name with $xml/element/name/text() ) return $xml &amp;lt;/fx-function&amp;gt; JavaScript &amp;lt;fx-function signature=&amp;#34;now() as xs:string&amp;#34; type=&amp;#34;text/javascript&amp;#34;&amp;gt; const now = new Date(); return `${String(now.</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-instance></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/model/instance/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/model/instance/</guid><description>Description Holds the data of the model. A fx-model may have as many fx-instance elements as necessary.
Attributes Name Description default credentials sets credentials policy - one of &amp;lsquo;omit&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;same-origin&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;include&amp;rsquo; same-origin id id of the instance for addressing in refs default shared boolean attribute to signal that the instance is shared with nested Fore elements src url to load instance from via http get type &amp;lsquo;xml&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;json&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;html&amp;rsquo; are supported by now xml xpath-default-namespace namespace to be used with unprefixed XPathes emtpy Shared instances By adding an shared attribute to an &amp;lt;fx-instance&amp;gt; that instance is shared with nested &amp;lt;fx-fore&amp;gt; elements and can be accessed and mutated as usual.</description></item><item><title>&lt;fx-submission></title><link>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/model/submission/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:41:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jinntec.github.io/fore-docs/elements/model/submission/</guid><description>Description Send and receive data.
Attributes Name Description Default credentials sets credentials policy - one of &amp;lsquo;omit&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;same-origin&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;include&amp;rsquo; same-origin id required: id of submission for referral &amp;lsquo;default&amp;rsquo; ref XPath reference pointing to the bound node root node of default instance instance id of instance when replace='instance'. Required when replace=&amp;lsquo;instance&amp;rsquo; into XPath expr where to insert response nodes into method http methods GET, POST, PUT, DELETE, url-encoded-post GET nonrelevant handling of non relevant nodes during serialization.</description></item></channel></rss>